<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Self Health</string>
    <string name="nf_weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="nf_date">Date</string>
    <string name="nav_graphfrag">Graph</string>
    <string name="nav_numberfrag">Number</string>
    <string name="save_button">Save</string>
    <string name="ma_btnWI">Log</string>
    <string name="faq_button">FAQ</string>
    <string name="ideal_weight_button">Ideal Weight</string>
    <string name="ma_btnChart">Progress</string>
    <string name="print_button">Print</string>
    <string name="clear_button">Clear</string>
    <string name="delete_button">Delete</string>
    <string name="help_button">Help</string>

    <string name="faq_fragment">
        <b>What is BMI?</b>\nBMI is a very basic tool use to divide people into weight classes.
        It is calculated by using a person\'s height and weight.
        BMI is not without flaws however as it fails to take into account the difference between muscle and fat, for instance it may look at a bodybuilder and classify them as obese based solely on the numbers.
        It may not be accurate for the elderly, professional athletes and pregnant women.
        However it should work by and large for the average person!\n\n
        <b>What are the health risks of being overweight or underweight?</b>\n
        There are a multiude of health risks that may crop up if someone is severely over or underweight.
        Overweight individuals, have a higher risk of cardiovascular diseases such as heart disease, high blood pressure, and more.
        It also increases the risk of metabolic disorders, musculoskeletal problems, and respiratory problems.
        Being underweight comes with it\'s own set of issues such as fatigue, weakness, anemia, low white blood cell count, bone health problems, and reproductive issues in women.\n\n
        <b>How can I lose weight in a healthy way?</b>\n
        Losing weight is almost deceptively simple, in it\'s barest form, you simply need to use more calories than you are intaking.
        You can lose weight by simply lowering your intake or upping your activity level and therefore use more calories.
        However you need to do so in a healthy and consistent manner.
        Crash diets may help you lose weight quickly but they often result in you gaining weight back as they are not meant to be a permanent diet. \n\n
        <b>How can I gain weight in a healthy way?</b>\n
        Gaining weight is slightly more complicated, as while the same basic principle still applies, you run into the risk of gaining just fat if you simply start scarfing down a bunch of food in order to surpass your caloric need.
        You should maintain a steady level of activity as you gain weight alongside a healthy diet in order to make sure you are not gaining purely fat.
    </string>

    <string name="weightHistory_instruction">
        <b>Basic Functions</b>\nPress the calendar and select a date, then enter your weight and press the save button.\nPress print to view previous entries.\n
        <b>Other functions</b>\nPress the clear button if you wish to remove all of your entries.\nTo delete a date entry, press the calendar then press the duplicate and then press the delete button.

    </string>
</resources>